(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T00:25:02.729263",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
AZKi 8th Birthday Live
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Cross Over 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Cross Over: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle
IRyS / 音乃瀬奏
IRyS / Kanade Otonose
みんな、こんあずきー！
Hello everyone, Kon'AZKi!
今日はAZKi 8th Birthday Live CrossOver 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦へお越しいただきありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much for coming to the AZKi 8th Birthday Live CrossOver: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle!
今回は平成赤チームと令和青チームの2チームに分かれて、アニソンで歌合戦をやっていきますー！
Tonight, we'll be splitting into two teams, Heisei Red and Reiwa Blue, to have an anisong singing battle!
今回ゲストの皆もそれぞれのチームに分かれて参戦してくれます！
All of our guests tonight will also be joining in, split across the teams!
ハッシュタグは #AZKi生誕ライブ2026 こちらこちらで、
The hashtag is #AZKi生誕ライブ2026, right here.
ぜひですね、赤チームここが良かったよーとか、青チームここが美しかったよーとかですね、たくさんポストお願いします！
Please make lots of posts like, "The Red Team was great here!" or "The Blue Team was so beautiful here!"
そしてサムネイルにも書いてありますが、新衣装のお披露目と、
And as mentioned in the thumbnail, we have a new outfit reveal,
重大告知もあるので、楽しみにしててください！
as well as a major announcement, so please look forward to it!
ということで、みんな盛り上がる準備はいいかー？！
With that said, is everyone ready to get hyped?!
おー！それでは、平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦開幕です！
All right! Let the Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle begin!
まずは平成赤チーム、
First up, the Heisei Red Team:
IRyS。
IRyS.
楽曲は、
Her song,
アニメ「新世紀エヴァンゲリオン」より、すべての始まりとなる1曲、「残酷な天使のテーゼ」。
from the anime Neon Genesis Evangelion, the song that started it all: "A Cruel Angel's Thesis."
続いて令和青チーム、
Next, the Reiwa Blue Team:
音乃瀬奏。
Otonose Kanade.
楽曲は、
Her song,
「シン・エヴァンゲリオン劇場版」より、すべてを終わりに導く曲、「One Last Kiss」。
from Evangelion: 3.0+1.0 Thrice Upon a Time, the song that brings everything to an end: "One Last Kiss."
時代を超えて交差する2つのメロディー。
Two melodies crossing over through the eras.
2曲続けてどうぞ。
Please enjoy both songs back to back.
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even if the blue wind knocks on the door of my heart right now,
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
you just gaze only at me, smiling.
そっとふれるもの もとめることに夢中で
So absorbed in searching for something to softly touch,
運命さえまだ知らない いたいけな瞳
with innocent eyes that don't even know destiny yet.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
But someday you will surely realize that on your back,
遥か未来めざすための 羽根があること
there are wings to aim for the distant future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will soon take flight from the windowsill.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with surging, burning pathos,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
embrace this universe and shine—young boy, become a legend!
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
Sleeping endlessly in the cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に呼ばれる朝がくる
a morning will come when only you are summoned by the messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
The moonlight illuminates your slender neck.
世界中の時を止めて 閉じこめたいけど
I want to stop time across the entire world and lock you away, but...
もしもふたり逢えたことに意味があるなら
If there is a meaning in the two of us meeting,
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
then yes, I am your bible for learning freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそしてはじまる
A cruel angel's thesis, and then sadness begins.
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
When you awaken to the dream of the form of life you embraced,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
shining brighter than anyone else, young boy, become a legend!
人は愛をつむぎながら歴史をつくる
People create history as they weave love together.
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
Unable to become a goddess, I will live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis, soon taking flight from the windowsill.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with overflowing, burning pathos,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
embracing the cosmos and shining bright, young boy, become a legend!
初めてのルーブルは なんてことはなかったわ
My first time at the Louvre was nothing special at all,
私だけのモナリザ もうとっくに出会ってたから
because I'd already met my very own Mona Lisa long ago.
初めてあなたを見た あの日動き出した歯車
The day I first saw you, the gears were set in motion,
止められない喪失の予感
bringing an unstoppable premonition of loss.
もういっぱいあるけど
Though we already have so many,
もう一つ増やしましょう
let's add one more.
Can you give me one last kiss?
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget,
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れたくないこと
something I don't want to forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
「写真は苦手なんだ」 でもそんなものはいらないわ
"I'm no good with photos," but I don't need such things,
あなたが焼きついたまま 私の心のプロジェクター
with your image burned into the projector of my heart.
寂しくないふりしてた まあ、そんなのお互い様か
I pretended not to be lonely; well, I guess we're both the same.
誰かを求めることは 即ち傷つくことだった
Wanting someone was synonymous with getting hurt.
Oh, can you give me one last kiss?
燃えるようなキスをしよう
Let's share a kiss that burns,
忘れたくても
even if I wanted to forget,
忘れられないほど
so much that it's impossible to forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh oh…
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
もう分かっているよ
I already know,
この世の終わりでも
even at the end of the world,
年をとっても
even as I grow old...
忘れられない人
You're the one I can never forget
Oh oh oh oh oh…
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
The one I can never forget
Oh oh oh oh oh…
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
The one I can never forget
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh oh…
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
The one I can never forget
Oh oh oh oh oh…
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない 忘れられない
Unforgettable, unforgettable,
unforgettable, unforgettable,
忘れられない 忘れられない
忘れられない
unforgettable...
I love you more than you'll ever know
Hmm…
Hmm...
吹いていった風の後を
In the wake of the wind that blew by,
追いかけた 眩しい午後
I gave chase on a dazzling afternoon.
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSS OVER
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover!
平成 赤チーム
Heisei Red Team:
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa!
楽曲は
Her song is:
アニメ『けいおん!』より ガールズバンド旋風を巻き起こしたクールなロックナンバー
from the anime \"K-ON!\", the cool rock number that sparked a girl-band phenomenon—
Don't say \"lazy\"
続いて令和 青チーム
Next, Reiwa Blue Team:
響咲リオナ
Hibisaki Riona!
楽曲は
Her song is:
アニメ『ぼっち・ざ・ろっく!』より 令和のバンドアニメの代表曲
from the anime \"Bocchi the Rock!\", the flagship track of Reiwa band anime—
星座になれたら
\"If I Could Be a Constellation\"!
時代を超えて響き渡るガールズバンドの系譜 2曲続けてどうぞ！
A legacy of girl bands echoing across eras—please enjoy these two songs back-to-back!
Please don't say \"You are lazy\"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
白鳥たちはそう
'Cause even swans, you know,
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
paddle frantically beneath the surface where no one can see.
本能に従順 忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct,
翻弄も重々承知
well aware of being tossed around,
前途洋々だし...
and with a bright future ahead...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
that's why I take a break once in a while!
この目でしっかり見定めて
Looking closely with my own eyes,
行き先地図上マークして
marking my destination on the map.
近道あればそれが王道
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road,
はしょれる翼もあれば上等
and if I've got wings to skip ahead, all the better!
ヤバ 爪割れた グルーで補修した
Uh-oh, broke a nail, fixed it with glue,
それだけでなんか達成感
and just that somehow gives me a sense of accomplishment!
大事なのは自分 かわいがること
The most important thing is to care for yourself;
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
if you don't love yourself, you can't love others!
Please don't say \"You are lazy\"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy!
能ある鷹はそう
'Cause even skilled hawks, you know,
見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks where no one can see.
想像に一生懸命
Giving my all to imagination,
現実は絶体絶命
while reality is a desperate struggle,
発展途中だし...
and still in development...
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
Which is why I might suddenly go off pitch
その目に映らないだけだって
Even if it's not visible to your eyes,
やる気はメーター振り切って
my motivation is redlining off the charts.
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always dreaming with all my might,
その分全力で眠って
and sleeping just as hard with all my might.
ヤリ ちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Sweet! Lost some weight, got carried away, and pigged out!
それだけでなんで？ 敗北感
Why does just that make me feel defeated?
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
Promptly revising my goals downward,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
being flexible and adapting—quick shifts win!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう
Just like peacocks, you know,
ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
showing off their beauty when the moment is right.
五臓六腑 満身 邁進
Pushing forward with mind and body,
願望は痩身 麗人
wishing to be a slender beauty!
誘惑多発だし…
There are so many temptations, after all...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why my willpower shatters so easily!
ヤバ まさか赤点!? いや ギリクリア!
Oh no, failing grade?! No, barely passed!
それだけでなんて全能感
And just like that, feeling totally invincible!
大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
What matters most is accepting yourself.
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
If you can't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当はcrazy
Because truthfully, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Just like swans, you know,
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
paddling furiously where nobody can see.
本能に従順 忠実
Faithful and obedient to instinct,
翻弄も重々承知
well aware of life's twists and turns.
前途洋々だし…
A bright future lies ahead, after all...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Which is why I take a break now and then!
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock is almost at six,
もうそこに一番星
and right there is the evening's first star.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on shadows, wishing to melt into the night on my way home.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search,
一つしかない星
there's only a single star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from hundreds of millions of light-years away.
いいな 君は
How nice it must be for you,
みんなから愛されて
loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕は ずっと一人きりさ」
"No, I've always been all alone."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
a fleeting wish on a star-strewn night.
きらめいて
Sparkling,
ゆらめいて
wavering,
震えてるシグナル
a trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
people looking up at the sky and pointing our way...
…指を差されるような
...like they're pointing up at the sky.
つないだ線 解かないで
Please don't untie the line that connects us,
僕がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling I may be.
もうすぐ時計は8時
Soon the clock will strike eight,
夜空に満天の星
a sky full of stars above.
何億光年 離れたところにはもうないかもしれない
Hundreds of millions of light-years away, they might already be gone.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The reason the beautiful moon brings me to tears
いつの日か 別れが来るから
is because farewell will come someday.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If we could gather together and become a constellation,
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
like a comet, these drifting soliloquies...
消えていく 残像は 真夜中のプリズム
The fading afterimages are a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If we could gather together and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my earnest wish could reach someone,
変われるかな 夜の淵を
I wonder if I could change, tracing the edge of night,
なぞるような こんな僕でも
even someone like me.
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away in the distance, we ended up meeting.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
It's karma, so we're bound to meet again and again.
雲の隙間で
Through the gaps between the clouds...
君と集まって星座になれたら
If we could gather together and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
let's spread across the night and paint our daydreams.
暗闇を 照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if we're not a full moon illuminating the darkness,
だから集まって星座になりたい
that's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
radiating multicolored light.
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't untie the line that connects us,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you may be.
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSS OVER 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦 平成 赤チーム
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSS OVER: Heisei vs Reiwa Anime Song Contest. Heisei Red Team.
ロボ子さん。楽曲は――
Roboco-san. The song is...
アニメ『円盤皇女ワるきゅーれ』より、ラブコメから生まれた儚い名曲、「Agape」。
From the anime "UFO Princess Valkyrie", a transient masterpiece born from rom-com, "Agape".
続いて令和 青チーム。
Next, Reiwa Blue Team.
水宮枢。楽曲は――
Mizumiya Su. The song is...
令和版アニメ『うる星やつら』より、夜の街を駆け抜けるダンストゥーン、「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」。
From the Reiwa anime "Urusei Yatsura", a dance tune racing through the night city, "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous".
宇宙から届いた2つのラブソング。2曲続けて、どうぞ！
Two love songs sent from outer space. Please enjoy both songs in succession!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって 聞こえる
No matter where you are, I can hear it.
君がくれる Agape
The Agape you give me,
力のかぎり Dive!
with all my might, dive!
みつめる 触れあう その時
The moment our eyes meet and we touch,
愛は 二人を 試している
love is testing the two of us.
Time is now
この世の果てまで
To the ends of the earth
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape love that you give me
力のかぎり Dive!
With all my might, dive!
信じる 応える その瞬間
Believing, responding—in that moment,
愛が 僕らを ひとつにする
love makes us one.
Time is now
どこまでも生きて
Living on, no matter how far
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape love that you give me
力のかぎり Dive!
With all my might, dive!
遠く
Far away,
どこまでも
endlessly,
響く
reverberating,
果てなく
without end.
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape love that you give me
力のかぎり
With all my might...
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape love that you give me
力のかぎり
With all my might...
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The Agape love that you give me
力のかぎり
With all my might...
Dive!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
Radio wave tempo ramping up, wildly electrifying!
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
[Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous]
あなたにもわすれたいことかなしいことあるのかしらね
I wonder if you have things you want to forget or things that make you sad, too.
識らない映画なのに涙をながすのはドラマチックが足りていないからよ
Crying over a movie I don't even know is just because there isn't enough drama in my life.
そんな愚にも付かないことくだらないこと考えてばかりね
I'm always thinking about such silly, pointless things.
雨が上がれば愛もその横顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
Once the rain stops, both love and that profile of yours will probably belong to someone else.
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部今夜のためよ
All this fake foundation is just for tonight.
なのに一体全体如何して如何して何故何故？
But why, why on earth, why is it?
不安定なカンテラ何処まで行くの
How far will this flickering lantern go?
あなた一切合切放り去ってもう
You've thrown everything away, so...
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, it's a Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, there's nothing that can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths will only make you feel melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
Come on, sweep me away right now, take on me!
はあ ちゃんちゃらおかしな法度ばっかで 食指がびくともしないわ
It's full of ridiculous rules that make me completely lose my appetite.
実態の無い感情放っておいたって 策略なんてありゃあせんのに何故
Even if I ignore these unsubstantial feelings, I have no hidden scheme, so why?
ああもう懲り懲りよ あたしの喝となる気質も じっと堪えて取り繕ってはとうとう臨界点
Ah, I've had enough! I kept enduring and hiding my fierce nature, but I've finally reached my limit.
年がら年中リップサービス鈍感カマしては辟易
All year round it's lip service; feigning numbness makes me sick of it.
どんがらがっしゃんフィールガールは涙の目にも鬼
A tumbling "feel girl" turns into a demon even with teary eyes.
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聴き取れない
Because of the music ringing in my head right now, I can't hear a single thing you say.
少しは真当なこと言って
Say something sensible for once!
回り出すターンテーブル ねえ全部忘れさせてよ
The turntable starts spinning—hey, make me forget it all!
だけど一体全体如何して如何して何故何故？
But why, why on earth, why is it?
不安定なカンテラ消えない儘ね
This flickering lantern still hasn't burned out, huh?
あなた一口両舌食い違ってもう
You're being two-faced and talking in circles, so...
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, it's a Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, there's nothing that can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths will only make you feel melancholy.
あたしを今…
Sweeping me away now...
冗談じゃないないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
No kidding, it's a Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, there's nothing that can be done.
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
How pathetic; I'll just wash away these emotions in the laundry.
あたしと確かめ合ってイエローマジック
Confirm the yellow magic with me.
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous.
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, there's nothing that can be done.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
Vague truths will only make you feel melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻っ攫って今テイクオンミー
Come on, sweep me away right now, take on me!
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSS OVER
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER
最後はチームみんなで歌い上げます
For the finale, each team will sing together!
平成・赤チーム
Heisei Red Team:
アニメ『とある科学の超電磁砲』より、今なお愛され続けるアニソンの王道、「only my railgun」
From the anime "A Certain Scientific Railgun," the timeless anime anthem: "only my railgun."
続いて令和・青チーム
Next up, Reiwa Blue Team:
アニメ『呪術廻戦』より、鮮烈でエモーショナルな青春ソング、「青のすみか」
From the anime "Jujutsu Kaisen," the vivid, emotional youth anthem: "Where Our Blue Is."
ステージでぶつかる電撃と呪力、2曲続けてどうぞ！
Electric sparks and cursed energy clash on stage—enjoy these two songs back-to-back!
放て！心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Unleash it! The dream engraved in your heart, leaving even the future behind!
限界など知らない 意味無い！
Knowing no limits—they're meaningless!
この能力が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
As this power radiates light, I send my distant feelings beyond!
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることしか
If looking back on the path I've walked...
出来ないなら…今ここで全てを壊せる
...is all I can do, then I can destroy it all right here and now.
暗闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの？
In city streets descending into darkness, how far can people stand and fight?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
From this accelerating pain, I can surely protect someone!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it right now!
身体中を 光の速さで
Coursing through my body at the speed of light...
At the speed of light throughout my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
a certain premonition raced through.
掴め! 望むものなら残さず
Seize it! Take all that you desire,
輝ける自分らしさで
with a shining authenticity of your own.
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I believe in the vow made that day,
この瞳に光る涙 それさえも強さになるから
because even the tears shining in these eyes will become strength!
立ち止まると 少しだけ 感じる切なさに
When I come to a halt, in the slight sorrow I feel,
戸惑う事 無いなんて 嘘はつかないよ
I won't lie and say I have no doubts.
宇宙に舞うコインが描く 放物線が決める運命
The parabola traced by a coin dancing in the air decides our fate,
打ち出した答えが今日も 私の胸を駆け巡る
and the answer I shot forth races through my heart again today.
Sparkling!
The shiny lights awake true desire.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 必ず
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it, without fail!
貫いてく 途惑うことなく
Piercing straight through without hesitation,
傷ついても 走り続ける
even if I get hurt, I'll keep running.
狙え! 凛と煌く視線は 狂い無く闇を切り裂く
Aim! A dignified and glittering gaze tears through the darkness without straying.
迷いなんて 吹き飛ばせばいい
Just blow away all hesitation!
この心が叫ぶ限り 誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
As long as this heart cries out, I won't let anyone get in the way!
儚く舞う 無数の願いは この両手に積もってゆく
Countless transient wishes dancing pile up in these hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは 重く深く 切ない記憶
What emerges in the torn darkness is a heavy, deep, poignant memory.
色褪せてく 現実に揺れる
Shaken by a reality fading in color,
絶望には 負けたくない
I don't want to lose to despair.
私が今 私であること
Being who I am right now,
胸を張って 全て誇れる!
I can hold my head high and be proud of it all!
Looking!
The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it, right now!
身体中を 光の速さで
At the speed of light throughout my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
a certain premonition raced through.
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Release it! The dream carved in your heart, leaving even the future behind!
限界など知らない 意味無い!
Knowing no limits, they're meaningless!
この能力が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
With this power scattering light, sending distant feelings far beyond!
青のすみか
[Song: Where Our Blue Is]
どこまでも続くような青の季節は
The blue season that seemed to go on forever—
四つ並ぶ眼の前を遮るものは何もない
there was nothing blocking our four eyes lined up side by side.
アスファルト、蝉時雨を反射して
Reflecting off the asphalt and the downpour of cicadas,
きみという沈黙が聞こえなくなる
the silence that was you becomes unheard.
この日々が色褪せる
Even if these days fade away,
僕と違うきみの匂いを知ってしまっても
and even if I learn of your scent that is different from mine,
置き忘れてきた永遠の底に
at the bottom of the eternity we left behind...
今でも青が棲んでいる
Even now, the blue still resides there.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue remains clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も
No matter what prayer or word,
近づけるのに、届かなかった
despite coming so close, it never reached.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
amidst the summer-like color streaming down cheeks,
きみを呪う言葉がずっと喉の奥につかえてる
the words to curse you remain stuck deep in my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
"We'll meet again, won't we?" a voiceless voice calls out.
昼下がり、じめつく風の季節は
In the afternoon, in the humid, breezy season,
想い馳せる、まだ何者でもなかった僕らの肖像
I reminisce on the portrait of who we were, back when we were nobody.
何もかも分かち合えたはずだった
We were supposed to be able to share everything.
あの日から少しずつ
Since that day, little by little,
きみと違う僕という呪いが肥っていく
the curse of being different from you has grown.
きみの笑顔の奥の憂いを
The sorrow deep behind your smile...
見落としたこと、悔やみ尽くして
I deeply regret having overlooked it.
徒花と咲いて散っていくきみに
To you, blooming and scattering like an unbearing flower,
さよなら
goodbye.
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue still dwells.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue remains clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も
No matter the prayers or the words,
近づけるのに、届かなかった
they brought us closer, yet never reached.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet romance,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
amid the summer-like color tracing down cheeks,
きみを呪う言葉が ずっと喉の奥につかえてる
the words cursing you remain stuck in the back of my throat.
「また会えるよね」って
"We'll meet again, right?"
声にならない声
In a voice that makes no sound.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のように
Like the grains of stars in an infinitely expanding galaxy,
指の隙間を零れた
they slipped through the cracks of my fingers.
はい、ということで、ここまで一気にノンストップでお送りしました！
All right, so we've brought you all these songs non-stop up until now!
いや、平成も、令和も、名曲ばかりでしたね！
Both from the Heisei and Reiwa eras, they were all such masterpieces, weren't they?
どうでしたか？好きな曲はありましたか？
How was it? Did you have a favorite song?
そして、みんな、どっちのチームが良かったかな？
And everyone, which team did you like better?
ええとですね、この...今の後ろのハートのステージね、
Well, you see, on this heart-shaped stage behind me right now,
こちらのハートに映し出された色で、どっちのチームが勝ったのかが決まります！
the color projected onto this heart will decide which team won!
ぜひ、みんなコメントでどっちが良かったか教えてください！
Please let me know in the comments which team you thought was better!
ええ〜？決められない？
Eh~? You can't decide?
いやいや、そこはちょっと決めて...あ、すごい、2色に分かれておりますけれども、
No, no, you have to choose... Ah, wow, the colors are split in two right now,
しっかり決めていただかないと。
but you really have to choose one!
今日は、平成VS令和となっております。
Today is Heisei versus Reiwa.
はい、ということで、勝ったのは、平成赤チームか、
All right, so the winner: is it the Heisei Red Team,
それとも、令和青チームか？
or is it the Reiwa Blue Team?
一体、どっちかな？
Which one could it be?
それじゃあ、行くよ？
Well then, here we go!
さあ、結果は...こちら！
The result is... this!
どっちかな？
Which one is it?
お？
Oh?
え？なんか、紫になっちゃったんですけど...
Huh? Wait, it turned purple...
紫って...紫ってどっちですか？
Purple is... which one is purple?
う〜ん、もうこれは、赤チームも良かったし、青チームも良かったということで、
Hmm, I guess since both the Red Team and Blue Team were great,
全てフュージョンして紫になってしまった...
they completely fused together and became purple...
ということで、みんなたくさん歌ったし、
So, with all the singing everyone did,
みんな最高だったってことにします！
let's just say everyone was the best!
いやなんか、みんなのおかげで、パワーが溜まってきた気がするなあ...
You know, thanks to all of you, I feel like power is welling up inside me...
気、気がする...！
I... I feel it...!
ふふふっ
Hehehe.
ということで、新衣装で〜す！
And with that, here is my new outfit!
え〜みんなのコ...
Um, looking at everyone's com...
...ベントが全部
...has completely...
AZKiの魔力に染まっちゃった！
...been dyed in AZKi's magical power!
見てください！どうですか？
Take a look! How do I look?
尻尾も...尻尾も生えてるんです！
A tail, too... I even grew a tail!
フリフリフリフリ
Swish, swish, swish, swish!
どうですか？
What do you think?
はい！ということで今回は...
Yes! So this time around...
小悪魔衣装を仕立てていただきました！
I had a little devil outfit tailored for me!
どうでしょうか？どうでしょうか？
How does it look? How do you like it?
魔力？魔王？ふふふ
Magical power? Demon Lord? Fufufu.
小悪魔です！
I'm a little devil!
はい！今回ですね新衣装はこちらの小悪魔衣装！
Yes! So my new outfit this time is this little devil costume!
可愛いでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
たくさんスクショも撮ってくださいね！
Please take lots of screenshots, okay?
ということで、この衣装でね、せっかくなので...
And so, since I have this special outfit on...
アニソンを歌っていきたいなと思います！
I'd like to sing some anime songs!
いや、もしかしたらね、ま、小悪魔ですから...
Well, maybe, since I'm a little devil...
この姿なら魔法とかも使えちゃうんじゃないのかな？
with this form, maybe I can even use magic?
ということで！
And so!
ではですね、次の曲、聴いてください！
Now then, please listen to the next song!
召喚ーーー！
Summonーーー!
自分の過去に囚われ迷って
Trapped in my past, losing my way,
そうじゃないよと言い聞かせて 全てを
Telling myself that isn't true, as if I could
自由に操れるかなんて
Freely control everything.
分からないよと 空は霞んで
The sky grows hazy, saying, "I don't know,"
正解はどこ？
Where is the right answer?
僕の手のひらに 残る大事なもの
The precious things remaining in my palm,
忘れない記憶 何度でも
Unforgettable memories, no matter how many times,
君を守り抜くと叫んで
I'll cry out that I'll protect you to the end.
巻き戻しの中 掴んだ愛はそう
Yes, the love I grasped in the midst of rewinding,
離しはしないから
I will never let it go.
散りばめた想い 今一度きりの願いへ
Scattered feelings, toward this one and only wish,
次への僕に 託したよ
I've entrusted them to the future me.
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
A promise made someday will become a guiding light,
誓いをさあ
Come, let this vow...
君のため
...be for your sake,
最期まで
Until the very end.
涙さえ力に変えてきっと 描いていた望む未来へ
Turning even tears into strength, toward the desired future we envisioned,
繋ぐよ
I'll connect to it.
想像を超える事態に 狂って
Driven mad by circumstances beyond imagination,
爪を立てては もがき足掻いて
Digging in my nails, struggling and squirming,
心は
My heart...
人生の過ちをもう何回
How many more times will it repeat...
繰り返しては 嫌いになって
...life's mistakes, growing to hate itself?
泣いてても
Even if I'm crying,
君の憧れは いつも輝いてた
My longing for you was always shining.
I'll come back (Yeah)
To your future (Go away)
僕は抗うだろう 運命に
I will resist fate.
Breaking out (Yeah)
Breaking down (Yeah Go away)
諦めちゃいないから
Because I haven't given up!
結ばれた意思は 独りきりじゃない強さへ
Tied together, our wills turn into strength that isn't alone.
紡いだ糸を
Pulling close...
手繰り寄せ 見つけた瞳は 理想を現実に変える
...the spun thread, the eyes that found it turn ideals into reality.
世界はそう
Yes, this world...
君のため
...is for your sake,
最初から
Right from the start.
胸に抱いた思い出とずっと あの日から続く決意で
With the memories held in my heart and resolve lasting since that day,
飛べるよ Redo
I can soar, Redo!
AZKi生誕祭、まだまだ行けますかー！
AZKi's Birthday Fest, are you ready for more?!
盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get hyped!
君がたとえ僕のこと
Even if you...
忘れても
...forget about me,
僕はもう忘れない 誰も傷つけない
I won't forget anymore; I won't hurt anyone.
消えそうな過去を 救い出すための時間よ
Oh time, to rescue a past about to vanish,
ここから始まれ
Start from right here!
始まれ
Begin!
巡りゆく一瞬を 今一度きりの願いへ
Turning each passing moment into this one and only wish,
確かに僕は 託された
It has truly been entrusted to me.
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
A promise made someday will become a guiding light.
誓いをさあ君のため
I'll make a vow, for your sake,
最期まで
until the very end.
涙さえ力に変えてきっと　描いていた望む未来へ
Turning even our tears into strength, surely toward the future we envisioned,
繋ぐよ
I will connect us!
わーい！
Yay!
ということで、聴いていただいて
And with that, thank you so much...
ありがとうございます！
for listening!
今日は小悪魔衣装になって、魔法で召喚しちゃいましたー！
Today I wore my little devil outfit and summoned a guest with magic!
召喚されちゃいましたー！こんあずきー！
I've been summoned! Kon-AZKi!
えー！ありがとうー！
Yay! Thank you!
ということでね、皆さんもご存知だと思いますが、
So, as I'm sure everyone already knows...
アニソン界のエース！鈴木このみさんに異世界転生してもらいましたー！
The ace of the anison world, Konomi Suzuki, has reincarnated into another world for us!
召喚されましたー！
I was summoned!
お誕生日をね、今日はお祝いしたいなと思って参りました！
I came here today because I wanted to celebrate your birthday!
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much!
ということでですね、一緒に歌った曲は『Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活』の
And so, the song we just sang together was from Re:Zero - Starting Life in Another World,
ファーストシーズンオープニングテーマ「Redo」でしたー！
the Season 1 opening theme, "Redo"!
イエーイ！
Yay!
いかがでしたか？
How did you like it?
あー、ドキドキしたなー！
Ah, my heart was racing!
私もめっちゃドキドキした！
My heart was pounding too!
なんか、「Redo」を人と歌ったことがあんまりなくて、
I haven't really sung "Redo" with someone else before,
あの、怖い顔をして歌ってないかすごい心配で。
so I was super worried if I was singing with a scary expression.
貴重な、貴重な経験ありがとうございます！
Thank you for such a precious experience!
あずきちと歌えて楽しかった！
It was so much fun singing with you, AZKichi!
えー！そう、あずきちって呼んでくれてるんですよ、みんな！
Aw! That's right, everyone, she calls me "AZKichi"!
あずきはね、このみんって呼んでるんですけど。
And I call her "Konomin"!
いや、そう、実はね出会いのきっかけはですね、
Well, as for how we first met...
いや、もうずっとあずきは元々大好きなんですけど、
I've always loved her for a long time,
このみんがね、あの『異世界かるてっと』の、
but Konomin, for Isekai Quartet...
そう！『異世界かるてっと３』のエンディングテーマ「キミイロボクイロ」のカルテットバージョンを作ることになりまして、
Right! We were making the Quartet version of the ending theme "Kimi-iro Boku-iro" for Isekai Quartet 3,
で、その時にあの会社の人から「誰か1人好きな人を召喚できる権利を差し上げます」って言われて、
and at that time, someone from my agency told me, "We'll give you the right to summon one person of your choice,"
「そんな機会あるなら、あずきちにお願いしてみたい」って。
so I said, "If I have that chance, I'd love to ask AZKichi."
私、ライブ元々見てたんで。
Because I was already watching your lives!
ええー！いいんですかー！
Whaaat?! Are you sure?!
いつかコラボしたいなっていう気持ちがずっとあったので、そこでラブコールをして叶いまして。
I had always wanted to collaborate someday, so I made the offer and it came true.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
まさかね、そんなことがありまして、そこからコラボ配信とか、
Who would've thought! That happened, and since then we've done collab streams,
あずきもね、このみんのライブ見に行かせてもらったりとか、
and I've gone to see Konomin's lives in person...
あとはね、ラーメンの...
And also... ramen...
ラーメンの汁をね、飛ばしました！
We splattered ramen broth!
あの配信の日にそういう話をしていて、すぐLINEを交換して、
We were talking about that on the stream day, exchanged LINE contacts right away,
すぐラーメンの汁を飛ばして、
and immediately splattered ramen broth together.
すぐそのあと焼肉にも行って！
Right after that, we also went for yakiniku!
油を飛ばし...
And splattered grease...
アフタヌーンティーにも行きました！
We also went to afternoon tea!
そうそう、めっちゃおしゃれなこともしたし、結構ね、
Right, right! We did super fancy things too, and pretty often...
そうなんです！なんと仲良くさせていただいております！
That's right! We've become such great friends!
もう濃厚なお付き合いで。
A very deep relationship.
そう、濃厚なお付き合いをさせていただいておりまして、
Yes, we've formed a very close friendship,
なんと今日、ついにバーチャル空間に来てくれましたー！
and today, she finally came into the virtual space!
初めてです！ありがとうー！
It's my first time! Thank you!
なんて楽しい空間なんだ！
What a fun space this is!
嬉しすぎるー！
I'm so happy!
なんかこの空間は魔法が使えるって聞いたんですけど本当ですか？
I heard you can use magic in this space, is that true?
使っちゃいますか？このみんは一体どんな魔法を？
Shall we use it? What kind of magic do you have, Konomin?
あの、私も僭越ながら1つだけ魔法を覚えてきたんですよ。
Well, if I may, I learned just one magic spell!
なんと！この日のために！
Wow! Just for today!
あの、これはでもみんなと一緒じゃないと完成しない魔法なんで、
But this is a spell that won't be complete unless everyone joins in,
ぜひあずきちへのラブを込めて、
so please pour all your love for AZKichi into it,
一緒に歌って魔法を完成させてください！
and sing along to complete the magic!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear あずきち
Happy birthday, dear AZKichi
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much!
Happy birthday to you
あずきち、仕上げをお願いします！
AZKichi, please do the finishing touch!
ふーーーっ！
*blows*
このみんは炎の使い手でした！
Konomin was a fire wielder!
おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
まさか歌までプレゼントしていただけるなんて、
To think I'd even get a song as a present...
もう、もうここで命尽きても...
I could just die happy right now...
ちょっと待って！ダメですダメです！
Wait a minute! No, you can't!
ダメです！命尽きちゃダメなんです！
No! You can't let your life end here!
あの、実は皆さん、今日重大告知と...
Actually, everyone, today we have a major announcement and...
書いてあると思うんですけどね サムネに
I think it was written in the thumbnail, but...
2人から 重大告知がございます！
We have a major announcement from the two of us!
やった！
Yay!
なんと！2人のオリジナルコラボ楽曲が出ます！
We're releasing our very own original collaboration song!
やったー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
ええー！いいんですか？ / いいんですか？
Ehh?! Is that really okay? / Is it really okay?
ということで タイトルは せーの！
And with that, the title is... ready, go!
最強未来衝動
"Saikyou Mirai Shoudou"!
という なんだか強そうなタイトルですね
That sounds like a really powerful title!
強い曲ですね！
It is a powerful song!
強い曲です
A powerful song indeed.
ということで なんと今日 初披露させていただきます！
And so, we will be performing it for the very first time today!
頑張ろうー！
Let's do this!
それでは早速 聴いてもらえますか？
So without further ado, will you listen to it?
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
それでは 聴いてください！
Alright then, please enjoy!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR
So just fly to the star
もっと WOW WOW
More, wow wow
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
Across the whole world, proudy glow
存在など言い切って無い無い
No point even defining our existence
壊れても関係ない
Even if it breaks, it doesn't matter
そっと触れるよ 生まれたての星へ
Gently reaching out toward a newborn star
囁きながら 願い重ねた 宇宙
Whispering in the sky where our wishes overlap
ほどけた軌道は 誰も知らない場所へ
Unraveled orbits lead to a place no one knows
微かな記憶と夢を この声に込めて
Pouring faint memories and dreams into this voice
今を 過去を
The present, the past...
未来を辿る
...tracing into the future
一瞬を 一生を
A single moment, a whole lifetime...
この手で掴む
...seized with these hands
超 BIG BANG!
Super Big Bang!
ただこのまま果てまで
Just going like this until the end...
溶けちゃって
...melting away
切り裂かれたいような衝動
An urge that makes me want to be torn apart
抱かれて 染まって 振り切って
Embraced, dyed, and shaken off
まだ ほら また
Still, look, once more
星を締め付ける
Clenching the stars tight
君と絡まってみようか
Shall we get entangled together?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動
It won't stop—our ultimate future impulse
ただ ただ
Simply, just...
剥がれ落ちてく
...peeling away and falling
広がって
Spreading out
咲いて
Blooming
駆け出して
Running out
飛んで
Flying
君と JUST FLY TO THE STAR
With you, just fly to the star
もっと WOW WOW
More, wow wow
無重力で DREAMY SHOW
In zero gravity, a dreamy show
運命など待ちきれない無い
Can't wait for something like fate
壊れても関係ない
Even if it breaks, it doesn't matter
そっと祈るよ 幾千年の星へ
Gently praying to the stars of millennia
彷徨いながら 僕ら出会えたんだ
Wandering through, we managed to find each other
燃え尽きる前に 誰も彼も急ぐよ
Before burning out, everyone rushes on
確かな希望と信念を この声に込めて
Pouring certain hope and conviction into this voice
星よ 光れ
Stars, shine bright
闇を照らせ
Illuminate the dark
歌よ 響け
Song, resound
遥か彼方へ
To far beyond
超 BIG BANG!
Super Big Bang!
引力にさあ導かれ
Guided by gravity...
この手を繋いだら
...if we hold these hands together...
それだけでいい
...that's all we need
聞いて！ 鳴り止まない絶唱
Listen! To the unceasing crescendo
愛して 焦がして 振り切って
Loving, burning, and shaking off
まだ ほら また
Still, look, once more
空を駆け巡る
Racing across the sky
君を狂わせてみようか
Shall I drive you wild?
止まらないで 絶対未来衝動
Don't stop—our absolute future impulse
ただ ただ
Simply, just...
生まれ落ちてく
...being born into the world
そばにいて
Stay by my side
触れて
Touch me
輝いて
Shine bright
消えて
Disappear
生きることは
Living means...
銀河を旅する STORY
...a story journeying through the galaxy
どこまでも走っていく
Running forever onward
どこまでも燃やしていく
Burning forever onward
どこまでも生命がある限り
For as long as life remains
叫べ
Shout it out!
伝えたい この淡い衝動
I want to convey this faint impulse
伝えたい この熱い衝動を
I want to convey this burning impulse...
衝動を
...this passion.
ゆけ ゆけ
Go, go,
ここから
from right here,
次元を超えていく
crossing beyond dimensions,
超えていく
crossing beyond,
crossing beyond!
歌え！この衝動はきっと
Sing! Surely this impulse,
抱かれて 染まって 振り切って
embraced, stained, and shaken off,
まだまだ ほら また星を締め付ける
over and over, look, tightening around the stars again.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall we entangle with each other?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動
It won't stop, the ultimate future impulse!
ただ ただ ただ ただ 剥がれ落ちてく
Just, just, just, just peeling away,
広がって 咲いて 駆け出して 飛んで
spreading, blooming, dashing, and taking flight!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR
So, just fly to the star,
もっと WOW WOW
even more, wow wow!
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
Proudly glow all across the world,
存在など歌い切って無い 無い
singing out our very existence, nothing's impossible,
壊れても関係ない
even if it breaks, it doesn't matter!
はーい！ということで、新曲を披露させてもらいましたー！
All right! And with that, we just debuted our new song!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！かっこいい曲になりましたね、このみん！
Thank you! It turned out to be such a cool song, right, Konomin?
ええ曲！
Such a great song!
A great song indeed!
ということでですね、『最強未来衝動』、本日、この後7月2日0時から...
So, "Saikyou Mirai Shoudou" will, starting today, July 2nd at midnight...
デジタルリリースされまーす！
...be released digitally!
わーい！
Yay!
ちょっと、せっかくなんで...
Since we have this chance...
この曲、実は、二人でね、二人で作詞を...
...the two of us actually wrote the lyrics together...
そうなんですよ！
That's right!
いたしました！
...for this song!
二日間、一緒に缶詰状態になって...
We spent two days holed up together...
一緒に缶詰になって部屋にね、閉じこもって、
Cooped up in a room together,
このみんと一緒に、作詞をするという貴重な、大変貴重な経験をさせていただきました。
I had the precious, truly valuable experience of writing lyrics with Konomin.
いや私も、すごい楽しかったし、仲も深まったんじゃないかって...
Well, I had so much fun too, and I feel like our bond deepened...
そう、仲深まったんじゃないか...
Yeah, our bond deepened...
気がしております！
...so much!
嬉しいです！はい、そんな楽曲ですので是非是非、隅々まで聴いて欲しいなと思います！
I'm so glad! Yes, so please definitely listen to every part of it!
お願いします！
Please check it out!
というわけで、今日はね、この世界に来てくれてありがとうございました！
Anyway, thank you so much for coming to this world today!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
どうでしたか？どうでしたか？
How was it for you? How did you find it?
正直言っていい？めっちゃ楽しい！
Can I be honest? It was super fun!
いや、もうなんか順応してる！
You've completely adapted to it!
そうなの。なんかね、何でも炎とか出せちゃうんだ...
I have! Like, you can shoot flames and everything...
そう、炎も出せちゃうし！
Yeah, you can even make flames shoot out!
え、ちょっとさ、最後にさ、二人でこのハートマークを作りませんか？
Hey, why don't the two of us make a heart shape together at the end?
やりたい！
I'd love to!
じゃあ行くよ？せーの！
Here we go, then! Ready, set, go!
いいんじゃないでしょうかー！
Didn't that turn out great?!
いいね！みんな撮れた？スクショタイムお願いしますね！
Nice! Did everyone get it? Make sure to take your screenshots!
はい！ということで、このみんと一緒にハートを作ったということで、
Yes! So, now that we've made a heart together with Konomin,
最後にこのみんから告知などありますか？是非！
...lastly, do you have any announcements, Konomin? Please, go ahead!
はい！
Yes!
えっと、まず7月11日に、アニサマ！
Um, first, on July 11th, Animelo Summer Live—
夏の、アニメの祭典が行われます！そちらに出ます！
the grand summer anime festival will be held! I'll be appearing there!
いや、すごいすごい！
Wow, that's amazing, amazing!
はい、フェスモードな感じで...
Yes, in full festival mode...
アニソンですよね！
All anime songs!
そう、アチチナ...あの歌で炎をバンバン出せたらいいなと思っておりますので...
Yeah, super hot... I hope I can fire off tons of flames with my singing...
ここでもね、現実でも炎を出してってくれます！
Just like here, she'll bring the fire in reality too!
お願いします！
Please look forward to it!
あとは、私あのライブが決まってまして、
Also, I have a live concert coming up,
11月7日土曜日に東京・大手町三井ホールにて...
...on Saturday, November 7th at Otemachi Mitsui Hall in Tokyo...
アニソンコレクションプラス、アニソンだけを歌うライブをやります！
...for Anisong Collection Plus, a live concert where I'll sing only anime songs!
なんですってー！
What a treat!
そう、だから今日あの、AZKiちゃんが、AZKiちが、今日アニソン？ずっと歌ってて...
Right, that's why seeing AZKi-chan—AZKichi—singing anime songs all day today...
そう、今日はね、アニソンをテーマにしたライブとなっております！
Yes, today's live concert was themed around anime songs!
「めっちゃいいじゃん！」って思いながら...
...and thinking 'This is so awesome!'...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
私もそんな1日を過ごそうかなと...
...I'm looking forward to having a day like that myself...
思っております！
...as well!
あの代表曲ばっかり流れる、そんな...
A show packed with signature hits...
そんな！行かなきゃ！
That sounds amazing! I gotta go!
ぜひ来てほしい！
Please come!
行かなきゃ！是非是非！
I definitely will!
ということで、ぜひ詳しくはアカウントをチェックしていただいて、一緒にアニソンまみれの1日過ごしましょう！よろしくお願いしまーす！
So please check my official account for details, and let's spend a day soaked in anime songs together! Looking forward to it!
行きたーい！
I wanna go!
はい、ということで、
All right, and with that,
えー残念なんですが、そろそろこのみんを元の世界に戻さないと、アニサマも...
...sadly, if I don't send Konomin back to her original world soon, Animelo Summer Live...
名残惜しい！
I don't wanna leave!
アニソンコレクションもできないので...
...and Anisong Collection won't happen, so...
またご飯行こう！
Let's go grab food again!
Let's definitely get food again!
ご飯行こうね！
We're going for food!
行こう、行こう！
Yes, let's go!
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあちょっとね、魔法を使って、このみんを元の世界に戻したいと思います！今日はありがとうございましたー！
Now, using magic, I'll send Konomin back to her original world! Thank you so much for today!
ありがとうございましたー！おめでとー！
Thank you so much! Congratulations!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
あー、消えちゃったー！
Ah, she's gone!
はい、ということでですね、サプライズ、スペシャルゲスト、鈴木このみさんに来ていただきましたー！
All right, and so, surprise special guest Konomi Suzuki joined us today!
今日のライブ、いかがでしたでしょうか？
How did you all enjoy today's live concert?
今日は本当にね、内容盛りだくさんで、
Today really had so much packed into it,
そうだ、このね、新しい小悪魔な衣装のことを
and right, I didn't get to talk much
あんまり話せなかったので、
about this new little devil outfit,
この後メン限でゆっくり見てもらえたらと思います。
so I hope you'll take a closer look during the members stream after this.
実は色んなアクセサリーや差分があります！
Actually, there are various accessories and variations!
ということで、ぜひメン限もよろしくお願いします！
So please be sure to check out the members stream too!
そして皆様、
And everyone,
最後にAZKiからみんなに嬉しいお知らせです！
finally, AZKi has an exciting announcement for all of you!
こちらをどうぞ！
Here it is!
傷ついた感情も連れていくから
Because I'll take even my wounded feelings along with me,
そっと響くファンファーレが 新しい未来を感じてる
the softly echoing fanfare makes me sense a brand-new future.
ほら 前向かって進むしかないでしょ
See, we just have to keep moving forward, right?
遠くまで
To far away...
届け この祈りよ 光となれ
Reach out, this prayer of mine, become the light!
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい 優しいという答えを
More and more, even little by little is fine, find the answer known as kindness...
もっと...
More...
お待たせしました！AZKi SOLO LIVE 2025「Departure」Blu-ray発売決定！
Thank you for waiting! The "AZKi SOLO LIVE 2025 Departure" Blu-ray release is confirmed!
開拓者のみんなと紡いだあのステージが何度でも見返せます！
You can rewatch that stage we created together with all the Pioneers again and again!
本日より受注受付が開始です！
Pre-orders start today!
続いて、告知2つ目！
Next up, announcement number two!
AZKiの歴史を彩るEP2作品の再販が本日7月1日より全国流通スタート！
The re-releases of the two albums that color AZKi's history start nationwide distribution today, July 1st!
対象タイトルは「Without U」と「Re:Creating world」です！
The titles are "Without U" and "Re:Creating world"!
最後、告知3つ目！
Lastly, announcement number three!
AZKi誕生日記念2026 グッズ情報！
AZKi Birthday Celebration 2026 Merch Info!
今回はお披露目された小悪魔衣装にちなんだグッズが盛りだくさんです！
This time, we have lots of merch themed around the newly unveiled little devil outfit!
イラストは信澤収先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
The illustrations were drawn by Osamu Nobusawa-sensei! Thank you so much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now then, let's take a look at the details!
まずはこちら！2層アクリルパネル！
First up is this! Double-layer acrylic panel!
小悪魔衣装のキービジュアルをアクリルパネルにしました！
We turned the key visual of the little devil outfit into an acrylic panel!
2層になっているので立体的に見えます！
Because it's double-layered, it looks three-dimensional!
ステンドグラスの神秘的な美しさと小悪魔衣装が見せるギャップをお楽しみください！
Please enjoy the gap between the mystical beauty of stained glass and the little devil costume!
続いてはこちら！ランダムラバーキーホルダー！
Next up is this! Random rubber keychain!
この後のメン限でも詳しく見せちゃうんですけど、
I'll be showing you in detail during the members stream after this, but...
今回の新衣装、実はバリエーションがいっぱいあるのでラバーキーホルダーにしてもらいました！
this new outfit has so many variations that we made them into rubber keychains!
君のお気に入りはどのAZKiかな？
Which AZKi is your favorite?
イラストはニャトラ先生に描いていただきました！
The illustrations were drawn by Nyatora-sensei!
続いてはこちら！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Next up is this! Plush keychain!
こちらも小悪魔衣装バージョンとなってます！
This one is also the little devil outfit version!
使い魔みたいな茶目っ気のある表情になっているので、ぜひ相棒として連れ歩いてください！
It has a playful expression like a familiar, so please take it along with you as your companion!
続いてはこちら！おそろいブレスレット！
Next up is this! Matching bracelet!
小悪魔衣装をモチーフにしたデザインのブレスレットです！
It's a bracelet designed with motifs from the little devil outfit!
日常の中でさりげなく推しを身に纏えるのはもちろん、
Not only can you casually wear your favorite in everyday life,
普段アクセサリーをつけない方には新衣装の再現コレクションとしてもおすすめのグッズです！
but for those who don't usually wear accessories, it's also a great collectible replicating the outfit!
続いてはこちら！ASMRボイス！
Next up is this! ASMR voice!
ボイスタイトルは「小悪魔チャーミング」！
The title is "Little Devil Charming"!
AZKiが小悪魔っぽく魔法をかけちゃう？そんなもしものお話のASMRボイスです！
What if AZKi cast a spell on you like a little devil? It's an ASMR voice depicting that hypothetical scenario!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！
And there are also full-set purchase bonuses!
信澤収先生イラストのAZKiのタロット風カードと特典ASMRボイスです！
An AZKi tarot-style card drawn by Osamu Nobusawa-sensei and a bonus ASMR voice!
数量限定バージョンは直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りです！
The limited quantity version includes a hand-signed autograph and foil-stamped replica message!
通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りです！
The regular version includes a foil-stamped replica autograph and message!
ということで、以上嬉しいお知らせでした！
And that concludes the exciting announcements!
この後はメン限でアンコールライブ！
After this is the encore live stream for members only!
まだメン限に入っていない方もまだ間に合うので、ぜひ入ってみてください！
Even if you haven't joined membership yet, there's still time, so please come join!
実は今回の新衣装、みんなにまだ見せていないあんな姿やこんな姿があるので、見に来てくれたら嬉しいです！
There are still looks from this new outfit that I haven't shown you all yet, so I'd love it if you came to see!
誕生日たくさんお祝いしてくれてありがとう！ライブも見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for celebrating my birthday! Thank you for watching the live stream too!
それじゃあ、この後メン限で会おうね！
Well then, see you in the members stream right after this!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!